<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Leandro&#39;s Code Cave</title>
    <link>https://iamleandrooooo.github.io/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Leandro&#39;s Code Cave</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://iamleandrooooo.github.io/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>SANDY - Malware Reverse Challenge</title>
      <link>https://iamleandrooooo.github.io/posts/sandy/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://iamleandrooooo.github.io/posts/sandy/</guid>
      <description>Challenge Description Author: John Hammond&#xA;My friend Sandy is really into cryptocurrencies! She&amp;rsquo;s been trying to get me into it too, so she showed me a lot of Chrome extensions I could add to manage my wallets. Once I got everything sent up, she gave me this cool program!&#xA;She says it adds better protection so my wallets can&amp;rsquo;t get messed with by hackers.&#xA;Sandy wouldn&amp;rsquo;t lie to me, would she&amp;hellip;?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RC4 Reverse Engineering</title>
      <link>https://iamleandrooooo.github.io/posts/rc4_reverse/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://iamleandrooooo.github.io/posts/rc4_reverse/</guid>
      <description>RC4 Reverse Engineering RC4 Overview RC4 is a lightweight stream cipher commonly used in malware for string decryption, binary unpacking, and encrypting network traffic.&#xA;When analyzing a binary that uses RC4, there are a few key indicators and areas worth examining.&#xA;No matter how much obfuscation is applied, typically if you find two loops responsible for initializing and scrambling a substitution box, it’s a strong sign that RC4 is being used.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Verification Clarification</title>
      <link>https://iamleandrooooo.github.io/posts/verificationclarification/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://iamleandrooooo.github.io/posts/verificationclarification/</guid>
      <description>Challenge Description Author: @resume&#xA;Difficulty: 🟡 Medium&#xA;One of our users received an unexpected email asking them to complete extra verification in order to download a zip file, but they weren’t expecting to receive any files.&#xA;Your task is to investigate the verification link provided in the email and determine if it’s suspicious or potentially malicious (“phishy”).&#xA;Note: If the verification link doesn’t respond when you visit it directly, try accessing it using a different method or tool.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Automating SQL Server Linked-Server Password Recovery with PowerShell</title>
      <link>https://iamleandrooooo.github.io/posts/sqlserverlinkedserverspasswords/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://iamleandrooooo.github.io/posts/sqlserverlinkedserverspasswords/</guid>
      <description>SQL Server Linked Server Passwords ⚠️ Disclaimer: Legal Use Only&#xA;This script is provided solely for legal purposes. Any use of this script for illegal activities or in violation of applicable laws is strictly prohibited.&#xA;I take no responsibility if:&#xA;You use this script for unlawful purposes. You encounter any legal consequences as a result of using this script inappropriately. This whole script can be broken down into 4 steps. The first step is enabling TCP/IP connections on all SQL Server Instances.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
